(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T00:57:39.478923",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
When was the last time we saw her?
She hasn't left her room in two weeks!
Does this mean... she doesn't love us anymore?!
Fear not, my friends!
Is that Jailboss? JAILBOSS?
Tonight, we infiltrate her bedroom!
Follow me! I know a secret passage.
You dare enter my room?!
Wait, no!
Don't mess with a girl's sleepover!
生まれた 赤い花
A red flower born,
只、孤独にゆらゆら
swaying all alone in solitude.
解答の無い儼
An unanswered riddle,
弁明は脆く愚かな結末
excuses lead to a fragile, foolish end.
礎にされた心は泣いてる
The heart turned into a foundation is crying.
両手から落ちるこの雫が
These teardrops falling from my hands...
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
You probably can't even see them, can you?
なら此処まで
If so, then up to this point...
悲しい声に
Driven away by sad voices,
コトバに、追いやらて
and by cruel words,
俯いたまま微笑む赤い花
a red flower smiling while looking down.
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
You probably can't see it, can you?
もう消えない傷
A wound that will never fade away...
風の吹く夜に
On a night where the wind blows,
散ってしまう花の色を
the color of the flower that scatters away...
貴方は知ることもきっと無いのでしょう
Surely you will never know it either, right?
底の底まで堕ちたら
If I fall to the very bottom,
黒い景色
a pitch-black scenery appears.
俯いたまま泣いてた赤い花
The red flower crying while looking down...
朽ちていく心の中まだ願ってる
Inside its decaying heart, it still prays...
ありのまま生きていたいと
"I want to live just as I am."
悲しい声に、コトバに、追いやらて
Driven away by sad voices and harsh words,
俯いたまま散りゆくアネモネ
An anemone scattering while looking down.
深く根を張る痛みが消えなくても
Even if the deeply rooted pain never vanishes,
足掻き続ける
I will keep struggling on.
何度だって
No matter how many times,
淡い想いに
towards those faint feelings,
手を伸ばして
I reach out my hand.
Little darling! My love, where are you?
Hello? Are you over here?
Oh, there you are! My darling!
Oh, you look so cute laying on my bed like that.
Isn't he just adorable?
Oh, I just want to squeeze him, but I'll leave him be for the time being.
Jailbirds, I have to welcome you to my room,
as this is a very, very special day.
Do you know? Do you remember that today is my birthday?
In case you don't know me, let me quick introduce myself.
Hiya darlings, this is Hololive English -Advent- Devilish Diva,
the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And I'm so happy to have you in here for my room 3D debut!
Being able to celebrate with you guys is so amazing!
But I thought it would be more fun if I had some friends with me. So, I've invited some very special people today.
Would you guys please come on in?
Yeah! Yay! What's up!
We're home! Yay!
Yay!
We're here today to celebrate Nerissa! Happy Birthday!
Thank you all for coming!
No, you're here for me, right? For me!
Look at your bed!
Yes! What do you guys think, by the way?
It looks like you!
I'm glad! I want to show off some details, because this is...
I know you guys have been here before, but this is the Jailbirds' first ever time seeing my room!
So, let me go ahead and point out some of the details.
First, because everyone's so interested in it, I want to highlight the bed area.
In this area, we have a lot of my personal plushies...
Cat!
And my cat! He does have another cat bed, but he likes to sleep there.
It's also very princess-y, right? Just like me, right?
Babygirl coded!
Babygirl coded! I also have a beautiful painting right above my bed.
And I see something else there. Is that a Jailbird?
No, no way! That's not a Jailbird, right?
Uh, who knows?
Then behind me, over behind FuwaMoco, there's this beautiful vanity area!
It's my kind of... It makes me feel even more princess-y.
You can see there's a bust of my head, because...
Wow! You have a bust made of yourself?
I know, it's important! It's important.
I also have a Renaissance painting scattered throughout the room, too. You might notice them.
I have little Advent references!
Oh, so cute!
There's a Pero hiding somewhere over here.
Up there, I have a Novelite.
And then over here, over by the vanity area, there's a little Geo!
Lots of little Advent references all around for you to enjoy!
So, yeah! That's it! That's awesome, right?
All right, time to leave! Bye! Thanks for having us!
Thank you! Thanks so much, we're leaving now!
Wait, you're leaving? What? You're not leaving!
Saw your cat...
I mean, okay. So are you gonna have us do anything then while we're here?
Yes! Well, I prepared a very special game today, actually.
I think you guys are gonna have a lot of fun!
I'm scared.
It's something a little out of the ordinary.
So today, you must treat me like your princesses!
Well, like your princess, actually.
I'm your princess, and you are my princes!
So, it's going to be a blind date. You have to make my heart flutter a lot,
and make me feel amazing on my birthday!
I guess that sounds like fun then!
I'm the one being rizz-ed in this game. I'm excited to see your unexpected sides!
So, I need to prep everything in my room, so I need you all to get over there!
No, no, no, just over there. In the corner.
In the corner?
Okay, I'm gonna set up.
Wait, why are we moving around? Are we supposed to get dizzy like this? I've gotta pull everything, okay?
Are we supposed to be spinning?
Just don't worry, the furniture's a little heavy!
Spin around! Spin around!
I have everything all ready!
Okay, what do you guys think?
A chair! A couch!
It kind of doesn't match the room's theme though, no?
It's fine.
I'm going to be sitting in this chair right here,
and I'm going to put on a blindfold, too.
Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry!
You guys can relax, okay? Relax!
And come close to me. You're so far away!
So, on this projector here,
there's going to be prompts with various questions and situations will appear.
So, you all have to answer them one by one.
Your voices are going to be altered with a voice changer.
Is it going to be cute?
Yeah, but I'm not going to be able to know who's talking.
So based on that, I won't have any preconceptions about...
anyone, because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So feel free to be extra romantic, okay?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, I'll do my best to be romantic then, hiya!
Let's start!
The name of the game is Cellmate's in Love!
The questions for everyone will be displayed on the projector screen, so please read them carefully.
But I must put my blindfold on now.
Okay, so I guess she won't know who's answering,
so the person should move quietly so she doesn't know the order.
And plus we have a voice changer!
Okay, well, we should probably line up now, huh?
Who wants to go first?
How about... I think you should go first.
Okay, we'll continue in this answering order then.
Now, give us the first question!
First Date!
It's been over two years since Rissa and I became friends...
But I think it's time to take our relationship beyond friendship!
I'm scared I might ruin what we have...
But I really want to tell her how I feel!
So gather your courage and finally decide to ask Rissa out on a date!
What would you say to ask her out,
and where would you like to go for your first date?
Try to ask her smoothly!
That was a lot!
Okay, so it's not just a hypothetical situation then, right?
So a lot on point, isn't it?
We all have to figure out how to ask her out!
Well, considering how you are now, right?
Well, are you ready then?
Okay, bye!
Nerissa...
You know, I've been thinking...
You're really important to me.
And I'd like to go out somewhere special together.
And I... maybe have some time...
just the two of us, you know?
So I was thinking...
maybe we could go to that cafe that you said you liked a few months ago?
Oh, your favorite, right?
Oh, we could go there and have a nice evening, and then maybe...
you know, once our tummies are all full,
then we can go on a bit of a stroll,
enjoy, you know, the city lights,
maybe the water...
Would you like that?
I would like that! That sounds so sweet!
Well, then, it's a date, okay?
Let's do it!
So romantic!
Okay, I did my best!
You did great! Yeah!
Good job, good job!
I'll go! I'll just go! I'll go!
Do your best! Show her what you're made of!
Hey, can we lower the mic a little bit for me? I mean...
No! You're love! You're cute enough!
This is kind of mean, isn't it?
Uh, whatever. Deal with it.
Okay, I'm ready. I'm ready.
Hey... Nerissa.
You and me... movies tonight.
Come or don't.
But if you don't, you're gonna miss out so much, baby.
You know what we're gonna do at the movies? We're gonna pick the scariest movie ever!
I...
I'm gonna be such a beeping wimp.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm gonna cringe at the jump scares.
I'm gonna be so beeping scared, you're gonna have to comfort me.
And then you're gonna have to put your arm around my shoulder,
and be like, "It's okay, sweetie. You'll be fine."
And then I'm gonna... I'm gonna nuzzle myself into your chest.
Yeah, while you comfort me.
And we're gonna bond over fear.
And it's gonna be the most amazing thing ever.
Oh my gosh, that sounds...
Come to the movies with me, or not, it doesn't matter.
That's also so enthralling.
Woah, I'm kind of interested.
Feels like a booty call.
But I'm a little scared, too.
I feel like I'm gonna have to be the one comforting you. I don't know how I feel about that.
That's the point! Yeah, that's the point.
Well, that's a good... Okay, let's move on to the next person then, how about?
Good job!
Yeah, nice try!
To the next person.
Who's next?
My turn!
After that, you have to show off.
Yeah, get going!
I'm waiting!
That was pretty good.
Thank you.
Impressive.
Rissa...
Well...
You know, we've been close for...
a little while now.
It's gone by in a flash, right?
But...
we've never really been able to hang out, just the two of us, you know?
Rissa...
I think I'd really like it if it were just...
you and myself.
And so I was thinking...
Maybe we could go...
get a massage together?
And then afterwards...
once you feel so much more relaxed...
and free...
We could go to a café!
A café that's very special to me...
because I know you're a little indecisive, too.
And...
then we could just chat...
and... more.
More?
Oh, that sounds so fun, too!
You guys are really speaking to my heart here,
with these cafés and dates and stuff.
I like it a lot!
I think we have one more contestant,
so Bachelorette Number 4, will you please take the stage?
Go!
Make it romantic!
Stomps angrily on the ground!
Yeah, I would go on a date with you.
No, thank you!
My lady...
Tips fedora...
Pulls out 10 million dollars in cash...
Waves it under your nose...
This is all for you. And you know what, not only that,
but I have 10 million roses in the ground right here!
They all don't die, just like my love for you!
That's how it's supposed to be!
You are as beautiful as the moon, and so bright,
so elegant, so...
in the night sky!
I love seeing you at night, man!
Wait, what are we doing for this date?
Oh, sorry! I forgot about the date!
Go on a date with me though!
Okay, you've convinced me.
I think all of you have successfully managed
to rizz me on a date.
So, there's our first question.
Yay!
Come back, come back!
Let me get my cash again, I dropped it.
I can't tell who my favorite is yet.
I think we're gonna need some more questions for me to be able to pick.
What?! Alright!
There's more!
All right, well, let's move on to the next question then!
All right!
We successfully asked Nerissa out, and she happily said yes!
Yeah!
Since it's our first date,
we want to make her feel special and happy, right?
Of course! Yeah!
Well, what kind of surprise do we have in store for our first date?
Ooh, a surprise!
Yeah, I love surprises!
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, the question is, are we gonna continue the story of our first date?
Yeah!
Let's do that!
Okay! Blindfold back on!
Okay! Yay!
All right, I'm ready to be rizzed.
All right, well, we're ready to rizz you.
Let's go in order of rizz then.
Okay, that's me!
Here I go!
She's so brave!
Wow!
So then,
during our date,
while we're walking along the water at night
with all the city lights around us,
suddenly...
You look at me, and...
Welcome to the stage!
You feel a bit panicked, and then suddenly...
...you see a bunch of mascot characters.
And they're doing a little bit of a dance...
And then, all of a sudden, one of them goes...
Woah!
And out comes me!
A bit of a surprise!
And I have roses.
And I say, "You're the character of my life..."
"...for you!"
That's so cute!
That's so romantic! Bachelor number one!
Thank you! Romance, yeah!
Okay!
Thank you!
All right, next up...
Go on, my lower-rizz champion!
All right, I got this.
Still, the mic is... Okay, well, whatever.
All right, Nerissa. After our date, you know...
...you have to take me home, because...
...I spilled my drink all over myself from being scared, 'cause you were comforting me, right?
So, afterwards, I take you home to my place.
And you know what we're gonna do? We open the door...
...and there's trash everywhere!
And that is my surprise, because I know everything about you, and I know that you love cleaning!
So, surprise!
My room is dirty and you have to clean it! And you love that so much!
And that's so romantic. We're like, "Yeah, woman, clean my house."
And I let you clean my house, and you feel so strongly about that.
You know, I do love to clean, especially for my friends.
However, I think if I was on a romantic date, it would not be at the top of my list.
But in the trash, there's like treasures for you that I put...
...I put in the trash! Like flowers! There's flowers in...
You'll have to dig for it!
I think I'd be turned off by that. I might be like, "Oh, that's cute," but...
...I might be a little... You did your best, so let's move on to the next one, how about that?
No one understands me! Where's the romance?
Okay! Who's next?
Did you like it? Good job.
I'm gonna do my best!
You know, here at this cafe...
...I guess you're really excited for the cakes that we ordered, right?
And, well...
I wanted to surprise you.
And I know there's one thing that you love very much.
So...
Nerissa, look into my eyes.
You see this here?
This is my smartphone.
Down! Down on the table!
Today, I'm giving you all my attention...
...because you're my princess.
And today, it's just you and me.
Woah! The rest of the world disappears when we're together for you? That's such a good surprise!
I love it so far, Bachelor Number 3!
All right, let's hear the last bachelor, shall we?
That was a good one.
Good job!
My lady, as we walk on the moon where our date takes place in...
...I reconstructed it from the ground up!
There's an amusement park in your honor, in your name!
Nerissa Ravenland!
And there are Jailbirds as far as the eye can see!
And each one serves you to the utmost ability they have.
You can even step on them, that's my surprise.
An entire army just for you!
Of fat flocks!
Oh my gosh! That is kind of romantic.
But I think they do that for me regardless, I don't think I need someone to set that up.
But they're Moon Jailbirds! It's like a whole different species!
Are they like white-colored, too, then? - Yes, and also maybe fatter.
Fat on my love for you!
What? You feed them with your love? - That's how they survive!
Well, thank you, Bachelor Number 4!
That was awesome! These are all awesome dates!
What about mine? - Well, it was a good attempt.
Everyone did so well!
Let's move on to the next question, shall we?
All right! Question of the day! "Say something to make Nerissa's heart race!"
Ah,
but even on this special date,
you feel frustrated that your "just friends" vibe has not gone away yet.
Um, now you want Nerissa to see you...
...more than a friend,
and you want her to think of you as like a... more of like a romantic interest.
So it's time to make your move!
How are you going to do it? Say something to win her heart!
Please do win my heart, Advent!
Please!
Don't look.
Is that possible?
Yeah, I'll put my blindfold back on and you guys can come up with...
...everything you want to say.
Need to think...
Well, thinking time's over. Bachelor number one,
would you please approach the mic?
Say something to make her more than friends.
Buy time, buy time!
Bachelor number one! Go, go Bill! Let's go!
Yeah... um, I'm Bill.
Bill?
Nerissa...
You know, we spent a lot of time together...
...and I think I know you pretty well.
And I hope that you would think the same of me, but...
I feel like, you know...
...I'd like to take things a step further.
You know, we're not just friends anymore, right?
So...
...can I... can I hold your hand?
Please, princess... You can hold my hand!
If you want to, I'll hold your hand!
That's enough!
Thank you! That's so sweet!
Hand-holding? That's such a big advancement of our relationship,
but I'd still like to hear Bachelor number two!
Good luck!
Trash!
You trash... I'm not trash! Your story...
Go, William!
I'm William.
All right, pave this. I'm coming over here.
Whoa! Is this consensual?!
You hear me in your ear, right? Yeah.
Smell me right now! I smell like trash?
I smell good. I smell good to you. That's the pheromones, baby!
If you think I smell good to you, that means you like me so much.
You're so attracted to me. So I think we should take our relationship to the next level. What do you say?
You're too close!
Is that a yes?
Maybe. I kind of...
...I enjoy that aggressiveness a little bit, I think.
It's fun!
You got to be successful! Gently!
Maybe just a little forceful, maybe just a little sudden.
You like that?
'Cause in your dirty room with all your dirty trash and your dirty flowers underneath the trash... I don't know.
Like, I feel like...
When it's just you and me, baby, in the moment, you will forget about everything.
I see. Well, let's move on to Bachelor number three!
You can do this. You can do it.
What's her name? Go, Matilda!
Matilda? Why was I Bill? Why not?
Nerissa... We had...
...some very nice times together, just you and me.
And, well...
...we're playmates, but...
...to me, we're a lot more than that.
You know, every time I sent you...
...one of those pictures that, um, maybe some duo with duo...
...that was just me with you...
There was a reason behind that.
And, well, today...
...I'd like you to know that.
So, um... I'm waiting for your answer, okay?
Cute! It's so innocent, too!
Thank you, Bachelor number three!
All right, we have just one Bachelor left. Bachelor number four, will you take the mic?
Steve, Steve, Steve!
Sir William, Matilda, and Steve.
He was always such a kidder.
Nerissa, my dearest...
I like you more than a friend.
Even... I don't know how you feel about me,
and regardless of who you choose,
whatever makes you happy,
I will honor it, and I will hope...
that you will always be happy with that person,
whether it is...
the beautiful Matilda,
the other people I've named...
I forgot who I named!
You're just so wonderful, and your smile is precious.
Tips fedora.
Walks away with my 10 million dollars of cash, depending on how you answer.
Oh my gosh! That's so sweet!
That's so earnest, too. Wow, I wasn't expecting that
from you, Bachelor #4, Steve!
No one ever expects that with a person with 10 million dollars.
No one ever expects that with a person with $10 million.
I know, yeah!
Well, how sweet! You guys all did so good! I feel my heart racing for sure!
And so, which one made your heart skip a beat the most, huh?
Well... the honest answer of who made my heart... stop...
...would be Bachelor #2.
Oh! That's pretty good, yeah!
But I don't... it's difficult to say.
I'll take that as a win! Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's difficult.
Again, it's still hard to pick. I think we have to ask a few more questions before I can settle on one of you.
Yes! Two more questions.
So, shall we read off the next one?
Okay, let me read the fourth question then! Okay, okay.
The sweet days you've longed for with Nerissa...
It's been two years since you finally confessed your love...
...and embraced something truly special between the two of you.
Everything seemed perfect, like a dream you never wanted to end.
But a tiny mistake on your part sparked a huge fight between the two of you!
With all your heart, apologize for the wrong you've done...
...and strive together to overcome this trial that threatens your love!
Okay, got it! So we've been dating for two years, and you guys have upset me.
So, won't you please apologize and make it all better?
I'll put my blindfold back on. So make things right between us, okay, you four?
Two years... Two years is pretty serious!
All right, Bachelor #1, it's your turn!
Okay! Here I go!
Nerissa... I'm sorry.
I know I hurt you very deeply...
...with all my...
Well, it wasn't meant to be like this, but...
...ultimately, it turned out this way.
My indecisiveness...
...my lack of action.
I know that you...
...the love of my life...
I should have done it.
I should have already proposed to you,
already made you mine...
...long before, but...
I'm sorry for hurting you this way,
for hurting you at your core, in your heart so deeply.
Could you ever forgive me?
What a cutie!
Still Bachelor #1, you managed to be so earnest and sweet!
You're really reaching to my heart!
Let's move on to Bachelor #2 and see what sort of answer they're going to give.
Hey Nerissa. I know I was gaming with the boys...
...and then you walked in, and you wanted attention...
...and I was like, 'Five minutes, I can't pause the game! It's an online game, Nerissa!'
But then you went away crying...
...but after the gaming session, I was like, 'Hmm, maybe I did do something wrong.'
Maybe I should have invited you to play the game with me.
So, I'm going to do something that I've never done ever once in my life.
I've never done this before... apologize.
Never apologized to anyone ever!
And I'm going to apologize to you now, so listen.
Sorry, I guess.
Do you wanna be my player two?
I'll play with you instead of the boys.
Come here, baby girl.
That's... I think that's good, Bachelor Number 2.
Let's move on to Bachelor Number 3.
Does she love that?
Thank you!
All right, Bachelor Number 3, to the mic, please!
Hey.
I know... things have been a little weird recently, huh?
I wanted to say something.
Nerissa...
I'm sorry.
I know... I know maybe I was acting a little childish.
I kept on saying things...
like you're stinky...
You know, maybe you took that personally, but...
it's just... I was teasing you...
because I love you!
I love you, Nerissa Ravencroft!
I'm sorry!
And I just wanted to say... is that...
you're stinky!
But... I love it! I love your stink!
That's enough!
Let's move to the last Bachelor, Bachelor Number 4!
What the heck?!
What a beautiful stench!
Okay, last one!
Hey, Nerissa.
It's me, one of the boys.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry that...
the other person and I were gaming instead of giving you attention.
Hello?
We were just having so much fun playing games together.
I should've been focused on you.
I'm crying right now!
Because I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry as one of the boys!
This is your heartfelt apology?
Thank you?
I guess in your universe, I have two boyfriends?
I'm dating both you and Bachelor Number 2?
I forgive you for that, super by the way!
Does Bachelor Number 2 forgive you?
Aw, very... very understanding lovers.
You understand we were gaming too hard, it was so great!
It's good! I got you!
Well, I think I'm getting closer to my answer of what...
one of these lovely Bachelors I'm going to pick.
But I think we're going to maybe do one... one more question?
What? I'm winning! Okay!
Let's move on to the final question!
And after this one,
Nerissa makes her decision
about who she chooses, so...
Nerissa...
Please answer carefully, okay?
Choose from the heart, okay?
From the heart.
From the heart!
Yeah. In fact, Nerissa, why don't you read the final question so you can finally see?
Okay.
Question Number 5:
My Eternity.
This is your moment, Bachelors.
Make the ultimate marriage proposal to me.
I've never made a marriage proposal before!
Marriage proposal!
Now's the time!
So, let me put my blindfold back on,
and I'm looking forward to seeing your answers, or hearing them!
Two years and she still can't see us!
You know, I...
the marriage proposal, should we really be going to the mic?
I guess you guys can do whatever you'd like.
Bachelor Number 1, will you approach?
Slow.
Thinking.
Slowly...
Thinking...
Bachelor Number 1, do you not love me or something?
Where are you? It's such a special day.
We've been out to dinner at my favorite restaurant.
Are you standing me up on such a special day?
Nerissa Ravencroft!
Yes?
What's so funny?
Will you marry me?!
Yes!
Just like that! Just like that!
Please!
Oh, she said yes! She said yes! She said yes!
Congratulations!
I mean, we've been dating for two years, what do you mean?
We're getting married!
We're getting married, but bachelor number two...
Just like that, it's over.
Boom.
I toss something on the ground, pick it up.
I know you're blindfolded, pick it up anyway, pick it up.
What?
Go.
Oh my god!
It was a ring! I put a ring on your finger!
We're engaged!
We're engaged now!
That's the wrong hand!
I love battery!
Get off me!
We're married!
That was so scary! I'm so scared!
Gotta go comfort her now.
Yeah, please, no more harassment, bachelors!
Let's move on to bachelor number two.
No more bachelor number two, bachelor number three, please!
Nerissa, wait a minute...
It's been many seasons that have passed...
...since we met.
Many memories...
...hard times...
...beautiful times.
Many tears we shed together as we watched the sunrise.
I'd like to spend many more sunrises...
...and sunsets together.
Will you be my everything?
Yes!
Aw, that's so sweet!
Bachelor number three...
You're so sweet!
I don't feel like I should clap.
All right, you don't have to.
We have one more contestant, bachelor number four, would you please...
What? What?
Approach?
What's going on?
My bro...
Yes?
You are like the bro-est of my life.
Wait, what the heck is going on?
Thanks!
We've been gaming for like two years or more.
Yeah, probably have been!
I love playing farming games with you.
How long?
I love playing shooting games with you, and you are...
...my number two, or my number one even, I'll be your number two.
How long?
I just love you so much, my bro.
Aw, thanks bro!
Will you marry me?
Well, I think you're disqualified!
Bachelor number four...
Get out of here!
Oh my god!
And with that, the questions are through.
Oh! Oh!
We've had some awesome love... awesome, maybe, if you can call it that, love stories born.
Some good, some bad.
From one to four...
...whose story did you like the most?
Please reveal the number, Nerissa! Who was the most romantic?
I'm going to go backwards, actually.
Drumroll, drumroll!
I think it's obvious which bachelor did not steal my heart today.
Oh, that way, huh? Drumroll, drumroll!
Bachelor number two, step forward!
You are disqualified!
All right, bachelor number four, step forward!
You're disqualified!
Somehow I feel like I knew it was you two.
I don't know what you're talking about! Come on, wifey!
This is the hard part now.
I'm between bachelors number one...
...and bachelor number three.
Who stole my heart the most?
Was it the earnest bachelor number one?
Or the very sweet bachelor number three who seemed to know me best?
Ah, I can't decide!
But if I had to pick between this impossible decision...
...I'd have to pick bachelor number three!
You can join us!
It's okay, you can join us! Yeah, we're married!
You can be the bride! We're the brides!
But I must say...
...knowing that each of you thought so deeply about a life with me...
...except some of you maybe...
...it makes me feel so special on my special day. So thank you for warming my heart!
Congrats! Yeah!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, I guess.
Oh, Fuwawa, you're so fluffy!
I love you. I love you!
Dada! Dada! Dada forever!
What a wonderful birthday this is!
I've even found a wonderful partner!
It feels like this next year of my life is going to be so amazing!
I know, my baby!
Hey! The flight is over!
Snap back to reality. Oh, let's play Twister!
Oh, yeah!
I got Twister ready so we can all play together!
Looking at it, it might be a bit tricky for all five of us to play at once, though.
Yeah, I think you might be right.
What should we do then?
Um, well, how about to make it fun, we can play one at a time?
You know what? Actually, I've just thought of a special rule for today!
Let's call the game: Posing Twister!
Posing Twister!
As the name suggests, the rule is to strike poses while playing Twister!
For example, if the instruction says "Right hand on red, cat pose!",
you place your right hand on red and do the cat pose. Once all four limbs are in position,
you can move just one limb to strike the specific pose. The time limit will be one minute,
and if you can keep your balance for the full minute, you can clear the challenge!
But if you lose your balance at any point, the game is over.
Quick question! Can the audience mess with the player?
Yeah, why not?
So, who wants to go first?
What? Well, we were just playing, so somebody else go first.
I guess I'll go first to kick it off, I guess!
I'll do my best, Mocchan!
I'll show you how it's done, okay?
I'll try my best to distract you, so good luck!
I've never played Twister before.
Really? First time then!
Well, you've got one minute, okay? Do your best!
Are we ready?
Then let's start! Go!
Okay, first up: Left foot on green, wolf pose!
Awoo~
Okay, next: Right hand on red, cat pose!
Faster, faster!
Nya~
Left foot on blue, cow pose!
Cow? Moo~
Moo~
All right! Right hand on red, hero pose!
Right hand on red, hero!
Right hand on red again. I can't help it!
Hero pose! Hero pose!
Left hand on yellow, happy pose!
So happy! Happy, happy, happy~
Now, place your left foot on yellow and express anger!
I'm furious!
So much rage! Bad dog! You did so good!
Yay! I did it!
I feel like I'm going to split apart!
You did so good! All right, Mocchan!
You passed with flying colors!
Don't fall! Are you okay? Good job!
All right, who's next, Mocchan?
Um, well... You get to choose!
Bebos! You're next because you made fun of me at the beginning!
I'll do it!
And because of that, I'm going to be your biggest distraction, okay?
How about I tell Bebos what to do then? Okay!
All right, let's start!
Right foot on blue! Now give me a graceful queen pose!
Oh my! Okay, Miss Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Left foot on blue!
Now do a lion pose!
Grrr!
Left hand on red! Oh!
Give me a rabbit pose!
Rabbit? What does a rabbit say?
Figured it out, I'm not a rabbit. Pickle!
Pickle!
Now place your right foot on green.
And go BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
Left foot on red.
Figure it out! Give us your best "grr" pose.
Grrr!
Right hand on blue.
Okay! Now kawaii, go kawaii!
Huh? 可愛いですよ！ 可愛いから許して...
Huh? It's cute! Please forgive me for being cute...
Good enough for me.
Did I win?
You didn't lose your balance, but I didn't think that was a very cute pose at the end. What about you, Shiori?
Not cute enough! But you did your best, so good job!
Yay!
Good job! What was that?
All right, you pick who's next, Bijou.
Okay, Shiori! You go next! I'll tell you what to do.
All right, boss me around!
Okay! Okay, Shiori, are you ready?
I guess so. Let's start!
Your left foot, yeah, put it on yellow!
Yellow, got it! I know you're gonna show us baby Bijou!
Baby!
Okay, now... again, left foot on yellow!
And... horse pose! Neigh!
Neigh! More horse! Neigh!
Okay, next is right hand on... Got it!
Now give us coolest prince pose!
Will you marry me, lantern-deer?
All right, let me spin this. Right foot on yellow... Okay.
And witch pose!
This is my broom somewhere here... Okay, there's a broom overall.
Okay, now left hand on red... Okay.
And do a bear pose!
I am already in bear pose. Grrr!
Okay, you gotta take your right hand...
Put it onto yellow, and you're gonna do a butterfly pose!
I am wiggling like butterfly! I'm flying!
Good job, Shiori! Thank you! That was so much fun!
You did so good, Shiori! Wow, you guys are all so good at this!
I know, right? You'll do great!
Well, Fuwawa, I think you're up! Okay!
I don't know if I'm gonna be good, but I can try! Do your best!
Okay, Fuwawa, go ahead!
Do your best now! Okay, let me spin!
Okay! Right foot on green, and do a hula dance move!
Right foot on green... Yeah, right!
Okay! Hula!
Left foot on yellow for dolphin pose!
Oh, no, need water! So funny!
Okay, next: right hand on red, fighting pose!
Right hand on red... Good luck with that!
I can't! Oh no!
You can do it! Reach, reach!
Oh, you did it! Oh, wait...
Your foot! Your foot, your foot!
Okay, okay, next! Right foot on yellow, puppy pose!
That's her default! You can't take your hands off!
Let it bleed! Wait, is that cheating?
BAU BAU!
Well, that's gonna have to do!
Yay! You know, she really did good! Thank you, puppy!
All right, Nerissa, it's your turn now!
Okay, I'm ready to... I'm ready to blow you all out of the water!
What? You think you can? No, I don't, actually.
All right, show us your flexibility! Are you ready? I'm ready! Let's start!
Okay! All right, first up: left foot on green with a...
Sexy pose!
All right!
Right foot on yellow, even sexier!
All right, left hand on blue, wet cat Rissa pose!
Meow!
Right foot on green, sea lion pose!
Swim, swim, swim!
Arf, arf! You don't know what a sea lion...
Right hand on blue, do one push-up!
Push-up!
Left hand on red, octopus pose!
All right, left foot on blue, pirate pose!
Arr!
You did so good! Thank you!
How do you like my posing, everyone?
That was real sexy poses!
Can we all do a sexy pose together?
Sexy pose, everyone! One, two... Wait, what is sexy?
Again! One, two, three!
Anime, wow!
Yeah, one more? One more.
One, two, three.
Very nice, ladies!
I think we're done with Twister.
Well, what should we do next then?
Actually, I was thinking maybe we could do karaoke together!
Yeah! I want to sing! Let me do it! Let's go!
And now, please enjoy... Dark Breath.
da da la la da la dark
ra pa pan pan pan
you will want it more, want it more
ey! you will love it now, love it
ra pa pan pan
風穴開けたんだ
I blew a wind hole
支配は始まった
The domination has begun
息はもう掛けたの
I've already cast my breath over you
but you don't know
自覚ないはずよ
You must be unaware
抑え切れない自力 制御不能な power
Uncontrollable power that I can't hold back
捕まえ見なよ 影形もない my heart
Try to catch my heart, which leaves no shadow or trace
I'm so crazy crazy in love
半信半疑な素振りは no no 心に従って
Half-hearted gestures are no no, follow your heart
忠誠心見せてよ 今こそ
Show your loyalty right now
baby don't let me down
ra pa pan pan pan
ey! gotta be kidding me 癖になるでしょ？
ey! gotta be kidding me, it's addicting, isn't it?
ra pa pan pan pan
ey! no love's killing me 足りてないのよ
ey! no love's killing me, it's not enough
oh no...
yes! dark breath 感じるでしょ 革命的存在を
yes! dark breath, you feel this revolutionary existence, right?
it's god's breath 渋滞感情 吹き去って
it's god's breath, blowing away pent-up emotions
ra pa pan pan pan
浅はかな言葉
Shallow words,
建前並べて
lining up superficialities,
何もないことぐらい baby I know
I know there's nothing behind them, baby
ほら 図星でしょ？
See, I hit the mark, didn't I?
枯れゆくこと受け入れた 鮮やかな flower
A vivid flower that accepted its fading
知りながら贈る笑顔に潜む姿
A figure lurking behind a knowing smile
心侵食される前に その身を預けて
Before your heart is eroded, surrender yourself
目覚めさせるのよ 永遠に
I will awaken you forever
I never let you down
ra pa pan pan pan
ey! gotta be kidding me 癖になるでしょ？
ey! gotta be kidding me, it's addicting, isn't it?
ra pa pan pan pan
ey! no love's killing me 足りてないのよ
ey! no love's killing me, it's not enough
oh no...
yes! dark breath 感じるでしょ 運命的衝動を
yes! dark breath, you feel this fateful impulse, right?
it's god's breath 脳内細胞 酔わせて
it's god's breath, intoxicating brain cells
ra pa pan pan pan
時代 未来なら見い出す
If it's the era or the future, I will discover it
意外じゃない I'm a genius
No surprise, I'm a genius
全知全能 like a Jesus
Omniscient and omnipotent like a Jesus
待ちわびてた 導くの
The long-awaited moment... guiding it all
全て染まり
Everything is dyed
誰もが悩む 桃源郷へと Change
Changing into a paradise that troubles everyone
天才の調合と
A genius's mix and...
手段はキリがない 万能な私ね
...endless means, I am truly omnipotent.
誰にも気づかれないけど
Though nobody notices,
仕向けるわ
I will bring it about.
癖になるでしょう
It'll become addictive, won't it?
誰も惹き立ててないのよ
Nobody is lifting anyone up.
そう Dark Breath ジェネレーション
Yes, Dark Breath generation.
普通じゃないスタート
No ordinary start.
いつかくれた色褪せぬ夢を 澄ませて
Purifying that unfading dream you once gave me.
Fuwawa!
Nerissa!
Are you ready?
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about a PaiPai Mask?
未来？ 恋の果て？
The future? The end of love?
残されたデータ 不明の金の山？
Leftover data? An unknown pile of gold?
あいつの気配がするものは
Anything that carries his trace...
未練ばかりで食えやしない
...is full of lingering regrets, utterly useless.
あたし粋な身体 化けて出れる
With my stylish body, I can transform and appear,
鏡の前で早変わり
Quick-changing right before the mirror.
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about a PaiPai Mask?
今夜も人は哀れ
People are so pitiful tonight as well.
踊れ 踊れ 踊れ
Dance, dance, dance!
乱れ髪に弾む胸
Disheveled hair and bouncing chest!
透明の罠に酔いしれて
Drunk on a transparent trap!
Shining spot! Shining spot! Shining spot! 照らしてよ
Shining spot! Shining spot! Shining spot! Illuminate me!
パイ パパイ パパパイ パパイ
Pai Pa-pai Pa-pa-pai Pa-pai
パイパイ仮面は話題沸騰
PaiPai Mask is all the rage!
パイ パパイ パパパイ パパイ
Pai Pa-pai Pa-pa-pai Pa-pai
女ごころ 舞い上がれ
A maiden's heart, soar high!
ほら ほら ほら 踊れよ
Come on, come on, come on, dance!
バンザイ バンザイ コインシャワー
Hurrah, hurrah, a shower of coins!
刹那を生きて色よ
Live for the moment, show your colors!
瞬間クライマックス
Instant climax!
浮世忘れて捨てる ダンシングハイ パイ ヤー パパイ
Forget the fleeting world, dancing high! Pai Ya Pa-pai!
ディスコティック クイーン Ah パイパイ仮面
Discotheque Queen, Ah, PaiPai Mask!
Pai! Pai! Pai! Pai! Pai! Pai! Pai!
Fuwawa!
Yes?
Singing a song together, what do we both have in common?
Uh... huh?
Come on, you say it!
Okay... Oppai!
Okay... Boobs!
Whoa!
悪い奴だと知りつつも
Even knowing he's a bad guy,
恋はもう目眩く度々
Love keeps spinning me around again and again.
愛のために血も青くした
I turned my blood blue for the sake of love,
あたしはトンマな道化師さ
I'm just a foolish clown.
虫ケラ共の情話
A love story of mere insects...
飛ばなきゃ虫ケラのままで終わっちまう
If you don't fly, you'll end up just a bug!
パイパイ仮面が解き放つ
PaiPai Mask sets free,
宵も羽ばたくよ
Flapping wings even in the night!
喰らえ 喰らえ 喰らえ
Take that, take that, take that!
けだものの夜 くせものの夜
Night of beasts, night of villains!
解った目をした あなたに当てられ
Struck by you with those knowing eyes,
Shining spot! Shining spot! Shining spot! 照らしてよ
Shining spot! Shining spot! Shining spot! Illuminate me!
パイ パパイ パパパイ パパイ
Pai Pa-pai Pa-pa-pai Pa-pai
パイパイ仮面は Born to be born
PaiPai Mask is Born to be born!
パイ パパイ パパパイ パパイ
Pai Pa-pai Pa-pa-pai Pa-pai
視線の先を射止んでる
Piercing right through where eyes lock on!
ほら ほら 揺らせよ
Come on, come on, shake it!
ラストアワーにバイブレーション
Vibrations in the last hour!
さあ 行け 立ち止まるなよ
Come on, go! Don't stop!
うたかたバブルモーション
Ephemeral bubble motion!
一瞬でゾーンに入る ダンシングハイ パイ ヤー パパイ
Entering the zone in an instant, dancing high! Pai Ya Pa-pai!
ディスコティック クイーン Ah パイパイ仮面
Discotheque Queen, Ah, PaiPai Mask!
今日もあいつはどこかの国で どんな悪さしてるやら
Wonder what mischief he's up to somewhere in the world today.
あたしはいつでも あんたの味方
I'm always on your side!
疲れた時には戻っておいで
When you're tired, come back to me...
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイ バイバイ仮面でどうかしらん？
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye, how about a bye-bye mask?
バイバイ バイバイ バイバイ バイ 黄金になっ調 舞い上がれ
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye, turn to gold and soar high!
ほら 踊れよ ダンシング ダンシング 今夜は
Come on, dance! Dancing, dancing tonight!
手をつなごう 生きろよ 瞬間 クライマックス
Let me hold your hand, live for this moment's climax!
浮世 忘れて耽る ダンシングハイ
Forget the fleeting world, indulge in a dancing high!
DISCOTIC QUEEN あぁ バイバイ仮面
Discotic Queen, ah, Bye-Bye Mask!
まわる まわる まわルーナ まわる まわる まわルーナ ルーナ
Spin, spin, spin-Luna! Spin, spin, spin-Luna, Luna!
まわる まわる まわルーナ まわる まわる
Spin, spin, spin-Luna! Spin, spin...
ぐるぐる まちまちに まちじゅうが まわる まわる あたま クラクラ
Round and round, all over the town, spinning around, head dizzying!
まつりが はじまり まわる まわる まゆを ひそめたら
The festival begins, spinning around, if you knit your brows...
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, spin around! Spin more and more round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる おどって
Round and round, spin around! Round and round, dance around!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる おどって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, dance around! Round and round, spin around!
まわりすぎたら せかいの くらやみが
If it spins too much, the darkness of the world...
みんな つつむ きょうふ 乱舞 だいこうふん
Envelops everyone, fear, wild dancing, great excitement!
まわる ちきゅうは まわり はじめて いくおくねん
The spinning Earth has been spinning for hundreds of millions of years...
いつまでも このまま まわる みんなに しあわせを
Spinning like this forever, bringing happiness to everyone!
まわり つづく まわルーナ ますます せかいが ぐるぐる まー
Spin-Luna keeps on spinning, making the world go around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, spin around! Spin more and more round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる おどって
Round and round, spin around! Round and round, dance around!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる おどって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, dance around! Round and round, spin around!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわルーナ
Round and round, spin around! Round and round, spin-Luna!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわって
Round and round, spin around! Spin more and more round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわルーナ ルーナ
Round and round, spin around! Round and round, spin-Luna, Luna!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわって もっと ぐるぐる まわルーナ
Round and round, spin around! Spin more and more, spin-Luna!
Let's go Advent!
ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ ぽ
Po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po, po!
まわる まわる まわ ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spin Luna
まわる まわる まわ ルーナ ルナ
Spinning, spinning, spin Luna Luna
まわる まわる まわ ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spin Luna
まわる まわる 地球を ぐるぐる
Spinning, spinning, round and round the Earth
またたく間に 街中が
In the blink of an eye, the whole town
まわる まわる あたま くらくら
Is spinning, spinning, making my head dizzy
幕が上がり 祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins
回れ 舞われ
Spin and dance around
眉を開いたら
When you open your eyes
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
もっと ぐるぐる 回って (もっともっと)
Spin even more, round and round (More, more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 回って (もっと)
Everyone, spin round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
もっと ぐるぐる 回って (もっともっと)
Spin even more, round and round (More, more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわ ルーナ (やぁ)
Forever spinning round and round, spin Luna (Yay!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Smile round and round, laughing along
もっと ぐるぐる 笑って (もっともっと)
Smile even more, laughing along (More, more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Dance round and round
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 踊って (もっと)
Everyone, dance round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Round and round, just like that
もっと ぐるぐる 回って (もっともっと)
Spin even more, round and round (More, more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Smile round and round, laughing along
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわ ルーナ (やぁ)
Forever spinning round and round, spin Luna (Yay!)
回り過ぎたら 世界の暗闇が
If we spin too much, the darkness of the world
みんなを包む 恐怖乱舞
Will envelop everyone in a frenzy of fear
大丈夫 守るから
It's okay, I'll protect you
ぐるぐる 地球は
Round and round, the Earth
回り始め 幾億年
Has been spinning for hundreds of millions of years
いつでもこのまま
Always like this
回るみんなに 幸せを…
Bringing happiness to everyone who spins...
まわりつづく まわ ルーナ
Keep on spinning, spin Luna
ますますます 社会が ぐるぐる
More and more, society goes round and round
ま〜…あれ？ (わぁ)
Spi~... wait, huh? (Whoa!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
もっと ぐるぐる 回って (もっともっと)
Spin even more, round and round (More, more!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 回って (もっと)
Everyone, spin round and round (More!)
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around, round and round
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin even more, round and round
mayday, mayday
mayday 声は届いてる？
Mayday, is my voice reaching you?
心がズキット痛いみたい
It feels like my heart aches sharply
baby なんて魅力的
Baby, how charming
魅せるテクニックはすぐにクラクラ
Your technique to captivate leaves me dizzy in no time
mayday それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's just not enough
すぐにもっともっと欲張るスタイル
A style that instantly craves more and more
hey hey もっと焦らしてよ
Hey hey, tease me even more
あなたの心に入りたいの
I want to enter your heart
ah 見え透いた甘い罠
Ah, a sweet, transparent trap
ah ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I fall for it?
ah 自在にコントロールしていたはずなのに
Ah, I was supposed to be in total control
クラクラっで酔っちゃいそうな 甘い匂い誘われ
Dizzy, lured in by a sweet scent that makes me feel drunk
フラフラっで寄っちゃうわ
Wobbly, I wander closer
あぁ もう help me...
Ah, someone help me...
逃げたいわけじゃなくて
It's not that I want to run away
これくらいがちょうどいいわ
This much is just about right
なんてもう キミの前じゃ絶対...
Saying that in front of you is strictly...
help me して
Please help me
mayday 舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't take the helm
気持ちがモヤッと晴れないし
My feelings are hazy and won't clear up
lady なんかじゃいられない
I can't just be a lady
今時の girl はもう ×× も ××
Modern girls are already XX and XX
絶対あるわけじゃないじゃない
It's not like it's impossible, right?
( can not believe )
(Can not believe)
絶対にただの勘違い
Definitely just a misunderstanding
( got attracted )
(Got attracted)
論外 手のひらの上で
Out of the question, being danced around
踊らされているこの感じ
on the palm of your hand like this
だってもう 溶け出すような
Because facing a body temperature
体温に見舞われ
that feels like it's melting me away,
なんか変 あたしじゃないみたい
I feel strange, as if I'm not myself
あぁ もう rescue me...
Ah, someone rescue me...
嫌々って漏れちゃうくらいに
Enough to let a reluctant sigh slip out,
あたしを困らせて
trouble me even more
なんかもああたしからは絶対...
From me, it's definitely...
rescue me して
Please rescue me
ねぇ どうして愛は悪戯するんだろう
Hey, why does love play such pranks?
ねぇ いつかはこの痛みも消えるの
Hey, will this pain fade away someday too?
本来は案外簡単に否定して
Originally, it's easily denied,
壊れちゃうけど 傷だらけの心は...
and easily broken, but this scarred heart...
気が付けば手を伸ばしちゃって その遠さ苦しくて
Before I knew it, I reached out my hand, that distance so painful
キミも手を伸ばしてくれたら...
If only you would reach out your hand too...
イタイ ここにいたいの cry
Painful, I want to stay right here, cry
落ち着く場所
A place to feel at peace
その手で触れてよ ほら mayday
Touch me with those hands, look, mayday
とべ、起こせ！
Fly, get moving!
願うは事故 一世一代 さあ何賭す？
All I want is trouble, only one chance, what do you bet on?
自問自答 勝つか負けるか ドローなんてないわ
Answer yourself, it's about victory or defeat, there can't be a draw.
幕開けるわ
Let's open the curtains.
カッチンして ラッキーマネー どっちも無理ー…
Catch it, lucky money, seems impossible...
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
You gonna pull out or no? It all depends on me, huh?
余裕で！振り切り 全betだぜ イエイ☆
Piece of cake! I'll bet it all and give it all I got! Yay☆
そこどけ！
Out of my way!
そう、このエースかっさらいうのはアタシだ
Yeah, I'll be the one to snatch this ace.
Stay もういい
Stay, I've had enough!
勝ったなら平常心ね プレイボーイ行け
If I win, my mind will be at ease, playboy, go.
Don't get in my way
じゃあね 黙って
So long, sit down.
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
Sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
はーもう フリーズキメてや
Alright, I freeze up locked in ice.
投げるのは賽？才？か匙か？
Throwing the dice? Talent? Or giving up?
そんな小さい尺じゃはかれないでしょう
You can't measure it with such a small scale.
そうでしょう セイ・グッド・バイや
Right? Right? Say goodbye, yeah.
あっちこっち そっち どっち？ nothing, nothing 病む yeah
Here, there, which way? Nothing, nothing, feeling sick, yeah.
道なき道より 闇々 嫌
Darkness is worse than a pathless road.
空回りしそう でも まだ 止めないで
Feels like spinning my wheels, but don't stop me yet.
あー のまれそう 声々 それぞれに Get one's way!
Looks like I'm gonna get swallowed up, voices guiding each in their own way!
アンタはここまで
You stay right here.
後ろだけ見とけ
Just look behind you.
カッチンして ラッキーマネー どっちも無理ー！
Catch it, lucky money, seems impossible...!
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
You gonna pull out or no? It all depends on me, huh?
余裕で！振り切り 全betだぜ イエイ☆
Piece of cake! I'll bet it all and give it all I got! Yay☆
そこどけ！
Out of my way!
そう、このエースかっさらいうのはアタシだ
Yeah, I'll be the one to snatch this ace.
Stay もういい
Stay, I've had enough!
勝ったなら平常心ね プレイボーイ行け
If I win, my mind will be at ease, playboy, go.
Don't get in my way
じゃあね 黙って
So long, sit down.
Huzzah! Woohoo! Hey!
Birthday, birthday! Happy birthday, Nerissa!
Thank you, Liz!
You better have a freaking wonderful rest of your day, because I'm monitoring you, all right?
You got it, Liz.
Thanks for the invite.
For Justice!
Oh, and she's gone.
Goodbye, Liz! I love you!
Good day, Nerissa Ravencroft, mother of my child! Happy birthday!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up!
いかにも蛸にもお腹goo goo
Octopus or whatever, stomach's going goo goo.
手に持つ少なめいざzun zun
Holding little in hand, now zun zun.
飯は食わねば寝る寝るneverナ
Gotta eat or else I'll sleep sleep never nah.
タイム・スリップいーya
Time slip, yeah!
ここどこ迷子でgo go go
Where am I, lost, go go go.
dancingダーウィンざんざん進化進行
Dancing Darwin, evolution and progress like crazy.
干渉あり人類発祥どうこう
Interference present, human origins and all that.
ァ良い感じそろそろ出発進行
Ah, feels good, about time departure and progress.
去る者追わ猿パパピパプ〜
Chasing monkeys who leave, papa pi pa pu~
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up!
欲しいモンはホラこれだろ旦那
What you want is right here, mister!
さぁワンワンワンワンワンっワンっ
Now, woof woof woof woof woof! Woof!
チキチキワッハー！
Chiki Chiki Wah-ha!
脳内全開yeahやっぱりっパッparty
Brain wide open yeah, party all the way!
笑って泣いて踊ればあいあいあっおー
Laugh, cry, dance, and it's ai-ai-ah-oh!
パンドラ開いてドヴァっで飲まれたraw
Opening Pandora, gulping down raw.
ご覧遊ばせ
Go on and enjoy.
あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン♪
A-cha-cha-i-cha-i-cha-i-parīn♪
おーわっあっアイアイ
Oh-wa-h ah, ai-ai
気分はhighとんとんたん
Feeling high, don-don-tan
おーわっあっアイアイ
Oh-wa-h ah, ai-ai
愛の間合いどんどんパン
Distance of love, don-don-pan
つながってんだ記録なんだgene & memeだ
Connected records, gene & meme.
連綿つむいだ犬猿人神
Continuously spun dogs, monkeys, humans, gods.
報酬いいんだ働いてんだ連勤なんだ
Good pay, working hard, consecutive shifts.
休みなし毎日が月月金土あーん
No days off, every day is Mon-Mon-Fri-Sat, ahh.
乱心ダーウィンざんざん淘汰進行
Deranged Darwin, culling and progress like crazy.
人類抹消あるでしょai暴走
Human extinction, might happen, AI runaway.
ァもう最深部そろそろ計画進行
Ah, now the deepest part, about time execution of plan.
もうゆびゆびまでワンツーっすりー
Already up to the fingers, one-two-three.
I'm dying! Thank you forever!
オーマイガ オーマイワイフ ようやく真理辿り着いた
Oh my god, oh my wife, finally reached the truth.
無限螺旋抜け無心で
Escaping the infinite helix, with a blank mind.
ほらウェーイほらウェーイ
Hey, whey, hey, whey!
はいっ！
Yes!
Happy birthday, Nerissa!
Put your hands up, put your, put your hands up!
欲しいモンはホラこれだろ旦那
What you want is right here, mister!
さぁワンワンワンワンワンっワンっ
Now, woof woof woof woof woof! Woof!
チキチキワッハー！
Chiki Chiki Wah-ha!
脳内全開yeahやっぱりっパッparty
Brain wide open yeah, party all the way!
笑って泣いて踊ればあいあいあっおー
Laugh, cry, dance, and it's ai-ai-ah-oh!
パンドラ開いてドヴァっで飲まれたraw
Opening Pandora, gulping down raw.
ご覧遊ばせ
Go on and enjoy.
あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン♪
A-cha-cha-i-cha-i-cha-i-parīn♪
おーわっあっアイアイ
Oh-wa-h ah, ai-ai
気分はhighとんとんたん
Feeling high, don-don-tan
おーわっあっアイアイ
Oh-wa-h ah, ai-ai
愛の間合いどんどんパン
Distance of love, don-don-pan
Put your hands up, ぷちょへんざっ
Put your hands up!
Put your hands up, ぷちょへんざっっ
Nerissa! Happy birthday!
And now, to wrap things up...
Up! Let's go ahead and introduce this year's birthday merch!
Please take a look at the set. There's also going to be a limited set...
...that comes with an autographed postcard!
So let's take a look at all the details!
First up! Can you believe it? I made a Jailbird onesie!
Isn't it so cute?
Oh, it looks so cozy! - Yeah, it's perfect!
If you want to let out your inner fat flock member...
...you can wear it to sleep, you can wear it out...
Who cares? You wear it wherever you want! It's a kigurumi!
So, do consider picking it up! Please!
All right, and the next item is...
...the Jailbird beanie!
Do you want to look cool?
Do you want to look nonchalant while also repping the Jailbirds?
Repping the fat flock?
Now you can with this bleeping beanie!
It even has a Jailbird embroidered on it! Look at the little horns!
It's so cool and cute at the same time!
And now for the third item!
Y'all, this is so cool!
Cool as ICE! As in like, sets of Jailbird ice trays!
You can make six different Jailbird ice cubes!
They're so cute! Look at all the expressions, too!
I can't wait to use this and put this in my matcha lattes!
What do you think? What are you going to use it first in?
Uh, I don't know! I think I'm going to put it in matcha lattes, too!
But I think I could just put it in my water, I could put it in anything!
You can just take them, you could chuck them, too!
Not at people, but like, at the floor. - At people would be okay, too.
At people! - Yeah. No, no, no, no!
Non-lethal weapon! - I mean, yeah!
It's cold damage! - Yes, more!
Ah, with this, "Day-Out With Nerissa" acrylic keychain!
You can take it along with you! Take Nerissa everywhere you go and take cute photos!
You know, it's like, uh... you're uploading it to...
...that my favorite app, "Nerissa Ravencroft". That's the best one!
I love it! - My favorite app!
It says, "My favorite app, Nerissa Ravencroft". So trendy!
Yes! This illustration is done by my mama as well!
So, it'd be awesome if you would share your photos with this item on SNS...
...using the hashtag #DateWithNerissa!
Please! - Did you... Did you just... - Never mind.
And of course...
...there's also a birthday set that includes a postcard and a bonus voice pack!
Along with these four items!
Only the limited edition comes with an autographed postcard.
So don't wait! Get yours now for your fat flock friends!
Now, what's this "Day-Out With Nerissa" bonus voice pack like, huh?
You have a preview?
I guess I could tell you a little bit about it!
Well, it's actually based off of the illustration.
So, uh, it's a day out, similar to the dates that you guys came out with.
I'm going to be going on a date with the Jailbirds to an amusement park!
So you can look forward to the shenanigans that ensue!
Shenanigans! Always shenanigans! Touch grass!
Anyways, I worked really hard to come up with all this merch so that everybody could enjoy it!
So be sure to grab yours as soon as it goes live!
The link's going to be in the description!
Well, this turned out to be such a wonderful birthday!
And I'm so happy that we could celebrate all together as well, it made it so special for me!
Yeah! And we also had Justice as guests, too, singing with me!
So, thank you Justice for coming and celebrating with me as well! And...
...most of all, thank you Jailbirds!
Thank you everyone! Have a good day!
Bye-bye!
[Message: Jailbirds, thank you for coming to my 3rd BIRTHDAY HERE in hololive! You've truly made the last few years of my life so incredibly memorable. I can't wait to see where this next year of my life with Advent, hololive, and you takes me! Thanks for always supporting me, and let's keep doing our best!!! -Nerissa]